Takaki Ishibashi

Tokyo, JAPAN +81-80-6791-9713 / itakaki0@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Highly Motivated Fullstack- Lead Software Engineer with 8 years of professional experience with Japanese, Chinese and English Communication skills. Able to Develop Integrated Management Software of Storage Area Networks for public and private sectors. Consulting, Agile development, Data Mart construction, and Data Analysis experience used to improve DX of system operations, and mobile / web applications for corporate clients. Client Facing Engineering experience in a wide range of areas (Infrastructure, UX and DX improvement, design, development, maintenance, and operations). E-commerce and Warehouse Logistics System Kaizen Project Management experience. Proof of Concept, Developing Voice and Image Recognition functions into E-Commerce applications. Able to Lead Overall Design, maintenance, and operation of Private Cloud Infrastructure and Security Architecture. Overseas experience with CERN (Switzerland) and Fermilab (USA) in the field of particle physics using accelerators.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Accenture PLC

Sep. 2018 - Present

Full Stack Engineer / Infrastructure Engineer / Team Lead

- Client Facing Solution Architect experience
- Team and project schedule management, Development framework design and construction, Application
 architecture design, Frontend of web application and API server design and implementation, DB design
 and implementation, User authentication function design and implementation, Session management
 function design and implementation, Development environment such as VPN server design and
 construction, Operation and maintenance of application infrastructure
- Data Management System, Data Warehouse System and Security Room reconstruction to client's on-premises environment
- Infrastructure development, maintenance and operation of CRM system, data mart and data warehouse
- Led overall backend implementation of real-time customer support UX, and linked SFDC user behaviour data with data from the client's data warehouse
- Management of E-commerce web application renewal project, including: Front End development, Image
 and Voice recognition search functionality, agile coaching, automation development for
 multilingualization (English, Chinese, and Finnish)
- Consulting / Engineering staff management, Training and Team Leadership

Reaktor Japan Co., Ltd.

May 2017 - Aug. 2018

Software Engineer / Web Engineer

- Client Facing Web / Mobile application, and data analysis Lead Engineer
- Development of a tracking system for a beverage manufacturer's point recharge mobile application
- Analysis of tracking data to solve the Bluetooth Low Energy communication problem between mobile application and vending machines
- Debugging communication problems in Finnish VR projects
- Development of mobile application's peripheral coupon content display function using vending machine location information
- · UX Improvement engineering

Hitachi, Ltd. Apr. 2013 - May 2017

Product Development Engineer / Infrastructure Engineer, Team Lead

- System and Infrastructure Development / maintenance for local government
- Development of HCS's (Hitachi Command Suite) NAT support function for enterprise storage NAT
- Development of JP1 v11's AWS autoscale support function
- Design and implementation for HCS's v7.9's private API
- Implementation of HCS's performance analysis GUI for multiprocessor blades in enterprise storage

EDUCATION

University of Tsukuba

Apr. 2007 - Mar. 2013

- Bachelor of Science
 - Physics
- Masters of Science
 - Physics

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages:
 - Bash, Bourne Shell, C, CSS, HTML, Java, JavaScript, PHP, TypeScript, Action Script, C++, Elixir, Go,
 Lua, MXML, Object-Oriented C
- Frontend:
 - o Flux, ReactJS, Redux, Angular, Cordova, Bootstrap, OnsenUI, Saas, Service Worker, WebRTC, flow
- Operating Systems:
 - Amazon Linux, WSL, Android, iOS
- Backend:
 - Apatch, Express, MySQL, NodeJS, Phoenix, Python, Tomcat, Unity, Nginx, Windows Command Prompt
- Cloud Infrastructure:
 - AWS, GCP, Vulture
- Database:
 - MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Frameworks:
 - Agile, RAD, Scrum, TDD, Waterfall, SDD, XP

GITHUB

https://github.com/xtaka